John A. Lomax and Alan Lomax papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Correspondence, 1925-1952 and undated
  - Subseries III: Alan Lomax, 1935-1969 and undated (Box-folder 3/115)
    - May 1940 (Box-folder 5/157)
      - H. M. Schweiger to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-09
        Little Red School House Music School
      - Harold Spivacke to E.O. Holland, 1940-05-11
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-13
      - Lesley Newton to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-14
        American Library Association; lecture notes
      - Hilder Cole to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-15
      - Gitel Pozman to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-20
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-20
      - Judith Waller to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-22
        NBC
      - Alan Lomax to Annabel Morris Buchanan, 1940-05-22
      - Ralph S. Boggs to Harold Spivacke, 1940-05-23
        University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill
      - Judith Waller to Alan Lomax, 1940-05-24
      - Alan Lomax to H.C. Darnell, 1940-05-24
      - Alan Lomax to Beatrice Sawyer Rossell, 1940-05-24
      - Harold Spivacke to Ralph S. Boggs, 1940-05-24
    - June 1940 (Box-folder 5/158)
      - Mrs. Samuel J. Brandenburg to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-03
      - Mrs. C. Paul Heavener to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-03
      - C.E. Tucker to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-04
      - Alan Lomax to Mr. O'Connell, 1940-06-04
        RCA Victor
      - Alan Lomax to Moses Smith, 1940-06-04
      - Annabel Morris Buchanan to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-05
      - Milton Ellis to John A. Lomax, 1940-06-06
        University of Maine speaking engagement for Alan
      - Moses Smith to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-06
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-07
      - Mack to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-10
        University of Chicago Choir
      - James B. to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-11
        RCA Manufacturing Co., Inc.; contract for Leadbelly and Golden Gate Jubilee Quartet services
      - Lionel Kaplan to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-12
      - H.C. Darnell to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-12
      - Alan Lomax to Mr. Jacobs, 1940-06-14
        CBS
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-06-14
      - Hugh Hodgson to Harold Spivacke, 1940-06-16
        University of Georgia music department
      - Columbia Lecture Bureau to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-18
        Contract
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-06-19
      - Harold Spivacke to Hugh Hodgson, 1940-06-19
      - Robert MacGimsey to Harold Spivacke, 1940-06-19
      - Robert P. Wetherald to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-20
      - Alan Lomax to Milton Ellis, 1940-06-21
        University of Maine
      - Alan Lomax to Lionel Kaplan, 1940-06-21
      - Richard Erstein to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-22
      - Harold Spivacke to Robert MacGimsey, 1940-06-25
      - Alan Lomax to Robert P. Wetherald, 1940-06-25
      - Mary Jo Wallace to Alan Lomax, 1940-06-25
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1940-06-25
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1940-06-26
        Pete Seeger film project
    - July 1940 (Box-folder 5/159)
      - David Kirby to Archibald MacLeish, 1940-07-08
        West Virginia State Board of Education
      - Robert P. Wetherald to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-08
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-07-08
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-08
      - Alan Lomax to W.E. Babb, 1940-07-09
        Rock Island Railway Co.; "Rock Island Line"
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1940-07-09
      - Alan Lomax to Helen Scott, 1940-07-10
      - Helen M. Metcalf to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-12
      - H.C. Darnell to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-12
      - Edward N. Waters to David Kirby, 1940-07-15
      - Robert P. Wetherald to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-16
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-16
      - Alan Lomax to Annabel Morris Buchanan, 1940-07-17
      - Isabel R. Scott to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-18
      - Richard Erstein to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-18
      - Harold Strauss to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-19
        Alfred A. Knopf
      - Alan Lomax to Richard Erstein, 1940-07-22
      - Archibald MacLeish to Annie Porter, 1940-07-24
        Greenville, South Carolina, Public Library
      - Alan Lomax to Annabel Morris Buchanan, 1940-07-24
      - Hal Davis to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-25
      - Isabel R. Scott to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-26
      - Harriet G. Brown to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-26
      - H.C. Darnell to Alan Lomax, 1940-07-31
    - August 1940 (Box-folder 5/160)
      - Alan Lomax to Isabel R. Scott, 1940-08-01
      - Mary Jo Wallace to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-01
      - Priscilla King Booram to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-03
        Worcester Womans' Club (Massachusetts)
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-03
        Archive budget
      - Alan Lomax to Harriet G. Brown, 1940-08-06
      - Alan Lomax to Isabel R. Scott, 1940-08-08
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1940-08-08
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1940-08-08
      - Annabel Morris Buchanan to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-10
      - Alan Lomax to Mitchell, James, 1940-08-12
        The New Yorker
      - Isabel R. Scott to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-13
      - Priscilla King Booram to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-14
      - Frederick A. Stokes Co. to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-14
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-15
      - Wilie Ross to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-19
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08-24
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08-26
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-27
      - Lee Marsh to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-27
        American Youth Congress
      - Alan Lomax to Beatrice Sawyer Rossell, 1940-08-29
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1940-08-29
      - Alan Lomax to Joseph Mitchell, 1940-08-30
      - Alan Lomax to Frederick A. Stokes, 1940-08-30
      - Archibald MacLeish to Alan Lomax, 1940-08-30
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1940-08-30
      - Alan Lomax to Hal Davis, 1940-08-30
      - Alan Lomax to Annabel Morris Buchanan, 1940-08-30
      - Joseph Mitchell to Alan Lomax, 1940-09-19
      - Alan Lomax to unidentified, 1940-08
        "American Songster" with Charles Seeger
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08
    - September 1940 (Box-folder 5/161)
      - Charles A. Thomson to Alan Lomax, 1940-09-10
      - Alan Lomax to Edward A. Ward, 1940-09-11
      - Alan Lomax to Isabel R. Scott, 1940-09-11
      - Alan Lomax to Lahmer, 1940-09-11
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1940-09-13
      - Alan Lomax to Robert P. Wetherald, 1940-09-16
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-09-16
      - Burton Paulu to Alan Lomax, 1940-09-27
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-09-27
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1940-09-27
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1940-09
        Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; undated
    - October 1940 (Box-folder 5/162)
      - Beatrice Sawyer Rossell to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-02
      - Alan Lomax to Jerome B. Wiesner, 1940-10-08
      - Lexie Dean Robertson to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-08
      - Gertrude Zwenig to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-12
      - Alan Lomax to Beatrice Sawyer Rossell, 1940-10-12
      - Alan Lomax to Burton Paulu, 1940-10-14
      - Alan Lomax to Charles A. Thomson, 1940-10-15
      - Mrs. L.S. Howard to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-16
      - Alan Lomax to Beatrice Sawyer Rossell, 1940-10-16
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1940-10-16
      - Howard M. Phillips to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-18
      - Alan Lomax to Howard M. Phillips, 1940-10-25
      - I.S. Becker to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-28
      - Merritt H. Coleman to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-29
      - Mrs. Billy Altizer to Alan Lomax, 1940-10-29
        Roanoke County Woman's Club
    - November 1940 (Box-folder 5/163)
      - Alan Lomax to Lexie Dean Robertson, 1940-11-01
      - Alan Lomax to Gertrude Zwenig, 1940-11-01
      - Alan Lomax to I.S. Becker, 1940-11-01
      - Alan Lomax to Merritt H. Coleman, 1940-11-01
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-04
      - Amelia C. Andrews to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-14
        encl. Widdicum Ware cards
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-15
      - Alan Lomax to Mrs. Billy Altizer, 1940-11-15
      - Alan Lomax to Roger Starr, 1940-11-16
      - Hans Christian Adamson to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-18
        American Museum of Natural History
      - Lavina S. Schwartz to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-18
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-19
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-19
      - Harold W. Kent to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-22
      - Valborg Kjosness to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-24
      - Alma Nielson to Alan Lomax, 1940-11-30
      - Roger Starr to Alan Lomax, 1940-11
    - December 1940 (Box-folder 5/164)
      - Angela M. Adams to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-01
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1940-12-02
      - Alan Lomax to Lee Hays, 1940-12-02
      - Alan Lomax to Hans Christian Adamson, 1940-12-03
      - Alan Lomax to Valborg Kjosness, 1940-12-03
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1940-12-03
      - Charles A. Thomson to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-07
      - Veronica Mileskay to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-09
      - Denise Chotas to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-10
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-11
      - Thomas Larkin, III to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-11
      - Archibald MacLeish to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-11
      - George Lee Kramer to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-12
      - L. Merrick to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-12
      - Alan Lomax to Charles A. Thomson, 1940-12-13
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-14
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-14
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1940-12-14
      - Alan Lomax to Baldwin Allan-Allan, 1940-12-14
      - Alan Lomax to Amelia C. Andrews, 1940-12-14
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-16
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-17
      - Robert P. Wetherald to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-19
      - Alan Lomax to Moses Smith, 1940-12-19
      - Columbia Lecture Bureau to Alan Lomax, 1940-12-26
      - Alan Lomax to Denise Chotas, 1940-12-30
        Embassy of Mexico
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1940-12-30
      - Alan Lomax to Thomas Larkin, III, 1940-12-31
      - Alan Lomax to George Lee Kramer, 1940-12-31
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1940-12-31
      - Alan Lomax to L. Merrick, 1940-12-31
      - Thomas Larkin, III to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-07
      - Lee Hays to Alan Lomax, 1940-12
      - Baldwin Allan-Allan to Alan Lomax, 1940-12
      - Anthony Strzilicki to Alan Lomax, circa 1940
        1938 Michigan recording trip
    - 1940 (Box-folder 5/165)
      - Miscellaneous notes and phone messages
    - January 1941 (Box-folder 5/166)
      - Arthur K. Moore to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-01
      - E.J. Foster to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-06
        The Record Exchange
      - Davidson Taylor to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-06
      - Amelia C. Andrews to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-07
      - Moses Smith to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-07
      - Archibald MacLeish to Library of Congress staff, 1941-01-08
      - Libbie Maney to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-09
      - Alan Lomax to Robert P. Wetherald, 1941-01-10
      - Alan Lomax to Amelia C. Andrews, 1941-01-10
      - Alan Lomax to Arthur K. Moore, 1941-01-11
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-01-11
      - Alan Lomax to Luther Evans, 1941-01-13
      - Robert P. Wetherald to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-14
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-01-14
      - Amelia C. Andrews to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-15
      - Ivalee Hobden to Harold Spivacke, 1941-01-21
        Farm Security Administration National Youth Administration for Texas
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-21
      - Alan Lomax to Willard Z. Park, 1941-01-27
        University of Oklahoma
      - Paul Gelinas to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-27
        CBS (Canada); enclosure
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-01-30
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-01-30
      - Joan I. Rayner to Alan Lomax, 1941-01-31
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-01-31
    - February 1941 (Box-folder 6/167)
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-02-04
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-02-04
      - B.B. Cubbedge to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-27
        American School of the Air fan mail
      - Alan Lomax to Ivalee Hobden, 1941-02-03
        FSA National Youth Administration for Texas
      - James L. McCamy to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-03
        U.S. Department of Agriculture
      - Alan Lomax to E.Z. Massicotte, 1941-02-03
        Palais de Justice, Quebec, Canada
      - Alan Lomax to Robert P. Wetherald, 1941-02-03
      - Alan Lomax to George W. Morgan, 1941-02-03
      - Alan Lomax to Libbie Maney, 1941-02-04
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-02-04
      - Alan Lomax to Sterling Fisher, 1941-02-04
      - Alan Lomax to Mrs. Harold, 1941-02-05, 2 copies
        Elizabeth Harold's mother
      - Alan Lomax to Joan I. Rayner, 1941-02-06
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-02-06
      - H.H. Pfeil to Fort Belvoir Commandant, 1941-02-06
      - Frank Donovan, Jr. to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-07
      - Alan Lomax to Mr. Hudson, 1941-02-07
        FSA National Youth Administration
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-02-10
      - Col. A.L.P. Sands to Col. I. Spalding, 1941-02-12
        enc. Songs
      - Burl Ives to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-13
      - James M. Savard to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-14
        Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; "Back Where I Come From" cancellation
      - Richard Erstein to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-18
      - Margaret Kennard to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-19
        Pratt Institute
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-02-19
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-19
      - Alan Lomax to Captain Hardiston, 1941-02-20
        White House Concert, 1941
      - Alan Lomax to Colonel Dunkle, 1941-02-20
      - Alan Lomax to Chaplain Lach, 1941-02-20
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1941-02-20
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1941-02-24
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1941-02-24
      - Harold Nestler to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-24
      - Alan Lomax to H.G. Crim, 1941-02-24
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-02-24
      - H.G. Crim to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-25
      - Alan Lomax to Archibald MacLeish, 1941-02-26
      - Alan Lomax to Elinor F. Inman, 1941-02-26
      - Alan Lomax to Col. A.L.P. Sands, 1941-02-27
      - Alan Lomax to Margaret Kennard, 1941-02-27
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-02-27
      - Alan Lomax to Richard Erstein, 1941-02-27
      - Maury Madison to Archibald MacLeish, 1941-02-27
      - Maury Madison to Alan Lomax, 1941-02-27
      - Alan Lomax to Lois Pollard, 1941-02-27
        enc. "Nobody's Darling But Mine"
    - March 1937 (Box-folder 6/168)
      - Helen Kwalwasser to Columbia Broadcasting Co., 1941-03-01
        Columbia Broadcasting Co.
      - Mary Jo Wallace to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-04
      - Elsie J. Kennedy to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-05
      - William H. Darrow to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-06
        "Alla En El Rancho Grande"
      - Ralph W. Magee to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-07
      - Elise E. Anderson to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-10
      - I.S. Becker to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-11
      - Mary Jo Wallace to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-12
      - Alan Lomax to Elsie J. Kennedy, 1941-03-15
      - Edgar F. Rogers to Harold Spivacke, 1941-03-17
        Library of Congress Personnel Office
      - I.S. Becker to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-18
      - Alan Lomax to Helen Kwalwasser, 1941-03-18
      - Alan Lomax to Maury Madison, 1941-03-18
      - Margaret Reed to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-18
        School District of Philadelphia
      - Alan Lomax to Leon Levine, 1941-03-19
      - Joseph Losey to Charles Seeger, 1941-03-20
      - Joseph Losey to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-20
      - Joseph Losey to Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge, 1941-03-20
      - Alan Lomax to Moses Smith, 1941-03-21
      - Alan Lomax to Margaret Reed, 1941-03-22
      - Mary Nan Gamble to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-24
        Library of Congress Murrell's Inlet materials
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-03-25
        National emergency
      - John Thompson to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-26
      - H.H. Ward to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-27
        E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc.
      - Moses Smith to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-27
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-03-30
    - April 1941 (Box-folder 6/169)
      - Alan Lomax to John Thompson, 1941-04-02
      - Alan Lomax to Moses Smith, 1941-04-03
      - Alan Lomax to Lydia Gross, 1941-04-03
      - William H. Darrow to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-04
      - Alan Lomax to H.H. Ward, 1941-04-05
      - Alan Lomax to Mrs. Frank Day, 1941-04-05
      - A.E. Garmaize to Macmillan Company, 1941-04-07
      - George P. Brett to John A. Lomax, 1941-04-08
        Macmillan Company; "Alla En El Rancho Grande"
      - Margaret J. Brandenburg to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-09
        Worcester Woman's Club (Massachusetts)
      - Margaret J. Brandenburg to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-09
      - Margaret J. Brandenburg to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-09
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Darrow, 1941-04-10
      - Michael Seeger to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-10
      - Alan Lomax to Elise, 1941-04-11
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-04-11
      - John Reynolds to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-14
      - Alan Lomax to John Reynolds, 1941-04-15
      - Willard Z. Park to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-17
      - Miles L. Hanley to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-19
        University of Wisconsin at Madison
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Nestler, 1941-04-22
      - Alan Lomax to Miles L. Hanley, 1941-04-22
      - Al Fields to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-23
        American Optometric Association
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-04-24
        Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; American School of the Air scripts
      - Marguerite Olney to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-24
      - Carleton Sprague Smith to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-25
      - Alan Lomax to Carleton Sprague Smith, 1941-04-25
        New York Public Library; undated
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-25
      - Alan Lomax to Carleton Sprague Smith, 1941-04-26
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-04-26
      - Fletcher Collins, Jr. to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-26
        Elon College, North Carolina
      - Alan Lomax to Al Fields, 1941-04-26
      - Harold Nestler to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-28
      - Richard Chase to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-28
      - Carleton Sprague Smith to Alan Lomax, 1941-04-30
    - May 1941 (Box-folder 6/170)
      - Lucie E. Breeden to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-07
      - Helen Hartness Flanders to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-13
      - Helen Hartness Flanders to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-26
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-27
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-05-28
      - T.J. Brandon to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-29
        Brandon Films
      - Duncan Emrich to Alan Lomax, 1941-05-31
    - June 1941 (Box-folder 6/171)
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-06-03
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-06-03
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-06-11
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-06-11
      - Josephine Lee to Alan Lomax, 1941-06-18
        International Student Service; encl. letter from Ernst Bornemann, 1941-06-10
      - Alan Lomax to Lucie E. Breeden, 1941-06-26
      - Alan Lomax to T.J. Brandon, 1941-06-27
      - Alan Lomax to Carleton Sprague Smith, 1941-06-27
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-06-27
      - Carleton Sprague Smith to Alan Lomax, 1941-06-30
      - Alan Lomax to Duncan Emrich, 1941-06-30
    - July 1941 (Box-folder 6/172)
      - Alan Lomax to Lawrence W. Chappell, 1941-07-02
      - Alan Lomax to Carleton Sprague Smith, 1941-07-03
      - Alan Lomax to Kay Dealy, 1941-07-03
      - Alan Lomax to Carleton Sprague Smith, 1941-07-08
      - Laura Boulton to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-09
      - Vance Randolph to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-12
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-07-14
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-07-14
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-07-14
      - Alan Lomax to Fletcher Collins, Jr., 1941-07-14
      - Alan Lomax to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-07-14
      - Edgar F. Rogers to Harold Spivacke, 1941-07-16
      - John H. Faulk to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-16
      - Davidson Taylor to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-17
      - Ingrid Johnson to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-17
      - S.W. Hinze to William H. Fineschriber, 1941-07-17
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-07-17
      - Alan Lomax to Vance Randolph, 1941-07-17
      - Alan Lomax to Sterling Fisher, 1941-07-18
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-18
      - Alan Lomax to Joanna C. Colcord, 1941-07-19
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Recording Laboratory, 1941-07-19
      - Alan Lomax to Ruby Pickens Tartt, 1941-07-19
      - William R. McDaniel to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-21
        Tennessee Writers' Project; enclosure
      - Jane Waring to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-21
      - Harvey Broome to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-22
        T.V.A. fieldtrip
      - Archibald MacLeish to whom it may concern, 1941-07-23
      - Alan Lomax to Sterling Fisher, 1941-07-23
      - Sterling Fisher to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-24
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-07-24
      - Fletcher Collins, Jr. to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-26
      - John H. Faulk to Elizabeth Lomax, 1941-07-28
      - Schriber, Thomas M. to Alan Lomax, 1941-07-29
        Maryland Casualty Co.; Choate
      - Alan Lomax to Sterling Fisher, 1941-07-30
      - Alan Lomax to Fletcher Collins, Jr., 1941-07-30
      - Alan Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1941-07-30
      - Alan Lomax to Ruby Pickens Tartt, 1941-07-30
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1941-07
      - Ruby Pickens Tartt to Alan Lomax, 1941-07
    - August 1941 (Box-folder 6/173)
      - Sterling Fisher to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-01
      - Mary Waller Bonelli to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-05
      - Fletcher Collins, Jr. to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-07
      - Ingrid Johnson to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-07
      - Hazel L. Muller to Nicol Smith, 1941-08-11
      - William S. Paley to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-20
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-08-21
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-08-21
        Proposed John A. Lomax/Tartt 1941 Southern recording trip
      - Alan Lomax to William R. McDaniel, 1941-08-23
        Tennessee Writers' Project
      - Alan Lomax to Harvey Broome, 1941-08-23
      - William H. Fineschriber to Alan Lomax, 1941-08-26
      - Alan Lomax to Fletcher Collins, Jr., 1941-08-29
    - September 1941 (Box-folder 6/174)
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-09-04
      - Harry Friedgut to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-05
      - Roxanna Wells to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-05
      - Alan Lomax to E.C. Ball, 1941-09-05
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-08
      - Joanna C. Colcord to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-10
      - Joanna C. Colcord to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-11
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-13
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-13
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-13
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-13
      - Dorothea N. Bestor to Harold Spivacke, 1941-09-18
        Buffalo Museum of Science
      - Ruby Pickens Tartt to Alan Lomax, 1941-09-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Luther Evans, 1941-09-24
    - October 1941 (Box-folder 6/175)
      - Harold Spivacke to Dorothea N. Bestor, 1941-10-03
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1941-10-10
      - Lawrence W. Chappell to Alan Lomax, 1941-10-15
      - Harry Partch to Alan Lomax, 1941-10-16
      - Alan Lomax to Sterling Brown, 1941-10-16
        Enclosed note from Sterling Brown, unknown recipient, undated
      - Alistair Cooke to Alan Lomax, 1941-10-17